In the daytime,
I’m Gabriel.
Just a normal man, with a normal life.
But I have a secret I must keep at any cost,
or all hope will be lost.
Miraculous! Fear is a cage. Hear the message, and serve the call.
Miraculous, yes you can change. The power of love will free us all.
Miraculous!
Hello and welcome!
If you're tuning in now, today's main event is, of course,
the new attack of Shadowmoth on Paris.
Luckily, Ladybug and Cat noir have saved Paris yet again.
Clara, you're live--
- Is it ready? Can we make the jump?
- There's a 92.7% statistical chance of landing in the world
where these source images originate.
I'm sorry. I can't stop them. They're coming.
We don't have a choice.
Fly my “Kamiko”,
and magnify the glimmer of hope that shines in Alya cesaire's heart.
Ubiquity!
I am “betterfly”.
I give you the power to connect to the parallel world we have located so we can find help.
With this gift, I am exposing you to many perils and placing a great burden on your shoulders.
Do you accept it for the greater good?
- I do.
After months of battle,
Super villain Monarch, who once went by Hawk Moth as well as Shadow Moth,
has managed to seize the miraculous that Ladybug had been guarding.
Monarch now threatens to attack Paris relentlessly.
We're heading straight for disaster. I knew it. I told you.
Shh. Be quiet, Mark. You're gonna jinx everything.
Fortunately, the people in Paris haven't lost hope and faithfully show their support for Lady--
You've reached Natalie Sancour's voicemail. I am not available at the moment. Please leave a message.
This power is so heavy, Plagg. I feel like I'm losing control.
I feel the same every time I see a slice of chesse.
It fades away eventually.
For real, Plagg. What if I ended up destroying everything around me without even meaning to?
For real?
Sometimes destroying is the best path to build a new. Trust me, it's worked for me more often than not.
- You really showed some self-control, Marinette.
- You-- you think?
- Of course. You didn't get the Kwamis back, but it's only a matter of time. I know it.
And here I was wondering how I could help you without superpowers, but you don't even need me.
Of course I need you. The one superpower you'll never lose is the power to be the best BFF ever.
After months of battle, supervillain Monarch, who once went by Hawkmoth as well as Shadowmoth,
has managed to seize the miraculous that Ladybug had been guarding.
Monarch now threatens to attack Paris relentlessly.
Did you hear that?
Now that Monarch has all the miraculous, I don't think I'll ever stop worrying.
Ladybug's already got one back. Before you know it, everything will be back to normal.
The people of Paris haven't lost hope and faithfully show their support for Ladybug,
who must be quite affected by what's just happened to her.
Ladybug! Ladybug! Ladybug! Ladybug! Ladybug!
I'm not sure I can do it this time, Alya. :(
Monarch's got all the miraculous and cat noir and i…
It's just the two of us again. I feel like I've tried everything.
I just don't know what to do anymore.
Marinette,
it's normal for you to have your doubts, but you can't give up hope and--
Alya?
Alya!
Forgive my intrusion, young lady. Please, don't be scared. My name is Betterfly.
I need someone to lead me to the holders of the miraculous of the Ladybug and the black cat in your world.
Ladybug and Cat Noir? but--
I don't know how to find them. I--
I don't know them.
I'm just Marinette, just a normal girl.
I beg you. Please, they're my last hope.
I'm not sure there's anything to hope for from Ladybug.
Marinette, what just happened?
You transformed into--
Ubiquity.
In the universe where I come from, Alya cesaire is my ally.
She connected her power to you
in order to open a gateway between our two worlds.
Uhhh?
UHH?!
Is this another one of Monarch's schemes?
Monarch?
I'm sorry , they made me open again.
I can't hold them back for long.
RUUUUN !!!
You can't stay here. They're merciless.
No, hey! Let go of me!
There! You can have your boyfriend back!
Hey! Don't gank the tail!
At least now it's being put to good use.
Even in this world, we find pictures of that self-centered Adrien Agreste.
Well obviously, He can only be perfect here, too.
A perfect stuck-up rat. No wonder you're a fan of his.
They must have gone out this way.
I'd rather go out with a bang!
And you are a ride back. Don't move.
Better fly. They tied me up.
You carried out your mission perfectly.
Thank you for everything.
I release you from the power I gave you.
Marinette? Marinette?
Everything okay, girls?
Uh, we're fine. Everything's fine, Ms. Dupain cheng.
We just, uh, we started playing a video game and the sound was too loud.
That's all!
Very well. Don't stay up too late, okay?
Sure thing. No worries.
Yes!
On which way did he go? He could be anywhere.
The city is so big! We'll never find him.
Lucky charm!
What is it this time?
A butterfly tracker….. Kind of.
These binoculars can detect butterfly pheromones.
Their smell, in a way.
Don't bother pretending to have a smart plan when all you have is luck.
And what's your plan besides showing off and destroying everything?
Ah, there it is.
Whatever happens, stay here where it's safe. No one should suffer because of a battle that isn't theirs.
Thank you for your help, little kamiko.
That's not an akuma.
An akuma?
Are you okay?
She'll use her lucky charm. I prefer intentional harm.
More direct.
>:)
But not discreet and even less clever.
He can’t be that far.
- Bogger fly, we know you're hiding here.
- Show yourself, otherwise...
- We'll turn this lousy world to ash!
I'm sorry that you got involved in this fight. Please, take care of yourself.
Stop! The people of this world haven't harmed you.
- You know what to do then.
- Hand over the miraculous you stole.
TIKKI: Are you okay, Marinette?
Yes. No, I don't know, Tikki.
Marinette, did you get away from that super villain?
I think he's a holder of the miraculous of the butterfly, Alya, except a superhero, not a villain.
Look around you. A better world than ours is possible.
- The only thing I'm interested in looking at is your destruction.
- And your imminent defeat.
They have the same powers as Cat Noir and you?
They're the holders of the miraculous of the ladybug and the black cat from one of the billions of parallel universes in existence.
And those two are not very nice versions.
Parallel universes? Why don't you tell me about this?
It's just, I've lived for billions of years in every single one of these universes simultaneously.
And there simply aren't enough hours in your lifetime to tell you even the tiniest bit about it.
So, I choose to stick to the basics and make the most of the time we have together.
The Supreme is manipulating you.
It's your fault. You shouldn't have stolen the miraculous from him.
The Supreme abuses his powers.
Power must be shared.
How can they use their powers repeatedly without transforming back?
Using the power of the miraculous draws vital energy from the Kwami, but also from the holder.
So there is a security system to protect those who are still a little too young.
Like you and Cat Noir, you transform back before it becomes dangerous for you.
- But for them…
-They use their miraculous for evil purposes.
It overrides the security system.
- No more automatic de-transformation, but the price to pay for that is...
- Terrible?
Alya, don't let my parents go into my room before ladybug has fixed everything.
You can count on me.
Thanks. Tikki, spots on!
Trap like a bug, you ugly butterfly.
Join the resistance. Everything can change.
This world is the proof of it. It's not too late for you.
The resistance ends here, with you!
What in the--?
I never thought I'd ever say this, but...
Let go of the butterfly man!
Another polka-dotted bug?
- The name's Ladybug.
- Whatever pest.
Hand over your miraculous.
They shouldn't be used for evil, only for the greater good!
Ugh, how corny?
Ugh, I'm gonna barf up a hairball.
Lucky charm!
PUSH!
Cataclysm!
Easy, kitty. Trying to keep my cool.
Think you're the cool cat?
Oh, is the itty-bitty kitty scared he might hurt me with his cute little paws?
Don't do it!
NO!
No black cat is as cool as this black cat!
Enough is enough!
The miraculous were not created to cause harm!
And what makes you so righteous, cockroach?
Are you with the super power police?
Lucky charm!
A traffic cone?
Oh no, I'm so scared!
Cataclysm!
Why do these akumatized heroes get all the magical powers and we don't? It's not fair.
They're not akumatized.
Then what are they?
They're Shadybug and Claw-noir.
And who the cat are you?
“Betterfly”. It's an honor.
- HUH?
- I know, I'll explain everything to you later.
They're gonna wish they were back in their world faster than a whip of my tail!
Watch out Cat Noir!
- Hey, what are you--?
- Celestia cat, I am Betterfly.
No, get out of my head!
I'm not your enemy. I only want to entrust you with the power to save us.
How do I know you're telling the truth? I don't know you.
I only work for the greater good. Like you, Celestia Cat.
Do you accept this gift I am offering you for the greater good?
I do.
Brace for takeoff!
They're getting away!
From you, maybe, kitty-catty.
Later, Loser!
Dear passengers, you may now unbuckle your seatbelt.
The cap’ts-ain and his crew hope you had a pleasant flight!
I’ll save you, don’t worry cockroach I’ll catch you.
Ooh, too bad I was this close.
Try that again, fleabag.
I'll have to pull myself together Emily.
- I may have more miraculous than Ladybug now, but not as much time.
- SHADYBUG: USELESS CAT
- huh?
Why are you always trying to steal my miraculous?
Like you never try to steal mine!
I'm just trying to get rid of you, fleabag.
- I'd be better on my own.
- OH Yeah?!
- SHADYBUG: Yeah!
- CLAW-NOIR: YEAH?!
Ah, I feel a dual source of anger and despair.
The magical jewels of the Ladybug and the black cat may finally be within my reach, my love.
Nooroo, Kalki, dual metamorphosis!
Fly to these hearts that are as black as mine, Megakuma!
Voyage!
I'll be the one to seize the miraculous of the butterfly in the end, and I'll be the one that supreme spares!
In your dreams!
Huh? A Kamiko!
Cataclysm!
You didn't make me so angry, Betterfly wouldn't have detected our emotions, kitty-catty!
Then DON’T GET ANGRY!
Fine, fine. Let's calm down.
So then, what do we do now?
It's a good thing I still have a brain and a lead.
I don't feel the emotions anymore. Or my Megakuma.
Dark wings fall.
She's freed herself.
She can't be far.
Where do you think you're going?
Stay here and help me search for a clue.
If the portal between our worlds opened here, there must be a reason.
You're not the boss of me, Detective Cockroach.
Ugh!
- Claws in.
- Spots off.
- What's wrong?
- Your world is so different, so beautiful.
You help each other, You’re partners.
In mine, any form of mutual aid is a crime.
Yet, you use your miraculous for good.
In my universe, ordinary people don't even know about the miraculous. It's a secret.
They all belong to the Supreme, who uses them only to perpetuate his own power.
The Supreme?
The name of the evil being who rules the world where I come from.
How did you find out about the miraculous, if it's a secret?
Sometimes. He entrusts them to the powerful of my world, all of whom have sworn loyalty to him.
I too was a part of this corrupt system.
In order to get something i wanted more than anything.
I stole too.
But i misused them,
and hurt the people i loved.
To redeem myself, I became better fly, because, like a moth, I have no choice but to fly in the shadows in order to give people hope.
Someone has to show them that we must revolt, that a better world is possible, provided that power is shared between all.
Claw Noir: I'm Lady Bug,
but my real name's Lazy Bug, because I'm lazy in every single dimension.
I wish you were Claw Noir because he’s the real cool cat.
Dear Diary, I can't believe I made such a blunder. I'll just die of shame this time for sure.
I had a presentation to do with Adrian, my Adrian.
Ugh. How can anybody be so disgustingly sweet?
Ugh, Cat Noir, we haven't known each other for very long, but it feels like we've been together forever.
Oh, Lady Bug.
Of course. I should've known.
I mean, like, we've been fighting villains together, right? Because there's absolutely nothing between us. He's just my partner.
Uh, my teammate is what I mean.
Ugh.
Now that I've seen your world, I know that my dream is not just a utopia, and you can help me reach it.
You know, our world isn't all that perfect. The one who holds your miraculous here uses it for evil.
And he just stole the miraculous I'd been guarding.
If I can't manage to defeat Monarch to save my world, how could I possibly help you save yours?
Because the values you stand for are good.
Because you are the positive incarnations of Shadybug and Claw Noir.
It may seem like they have more power than you, but they don't have your strength, because they know nothing about trust and friendship.
I should be as distraught as you. In my world, I'm hunted relentlessly. No one believes in heroes. Everyone is afraid of the Supreme.
I am so lonely.
How do you keep from giving up?
I hold onto the one thing I have.
Hope.
The hope for a better world.
The hope that people can evolve. For a single decision that can change an entire lifetime.
Plagg, do you think that the other holder of my miraculous could be that other world's me?
Well, you know. When two cheeses are made from the same milk, they can taste very different depending on how matured they are.
So, I guess that's a possibility, yes.
Tikki, do you really think that the person behind that evil Shadybug's mask could be me?
The girls were here for me. As always, they really are the best. They inspire me every day. Each one in their own way.
Alya and me, we're BFFs. It's so amazing to have a best friend like her. We're super close, you know. She's always there for me.
Tikki quickly became my friend. She always looks on the bright side and restores my confidence when I feel all is lost.
The first thing that comes to my mind when describing my mom is how calm and gentle she is.
Dear Diary,
I finally know why Hawk Moth wants our magic jewels so badly.
By combining my miraculous of a ladybug with the one of the black cat, you get to make a wish.
But for that wish to come true, there would be a price to pay.
For example,
If a robot became human, then someone would have to lose their humanity in return.
That's why we can never give up on our miraculous. No one must make a wish. The balance of the universe is at stake.
Lucky charm.
Cata--
Shhh.
Adrien Agreste?
Host: Tonight, on “Never Too Late to Do Good”, we receive one of the most influential people in all of Paris.
Mr. \ Mayor André Bourgeois!
Mayor: Thank you, thank you. The honor is mine. Good evening, everyone.
Ugh, makeup. Obviously, I should have guessed.
Blots off.
You know me?
Never mind.
Tikki, Plagg, reveal yourselves!
Why fight to get a better life when I could just switch with someone else's in another world?
(Gimmi), reveal yourself!
Host: The one and only Mr. Banana is joining us today.
What do you think of Ladybug losing the miraculous?
Stay peachy!
Tom? Tom? We fell asleep. Come on, let's go to bed.
Ms. Dupain-Cheng: Hold on, I forgot my phone.
Only the supreme divines reality.
Reality is the supreme.
Marinette? Is everything all right?
Yeah, whatever. Just get off my back.
Are you sure you're okay, sweetheart?
Yes, I'm okay. I...
Sorry, Mommy dear. I just dropped my sewing machine, but it's fine.
It's just…
slightly damaged.
Don't worry, sweetie. We'll take care of it. Broken things can always be fixed.
Good night, sweetie. I love you.
- I… love you too…, Mom.
- Wish Alya a good night for me.
Tikki, blots on.
Get to work, Mouser.
We've got to take the butterfly miraculous back. That's all we have left anyway.
Plag, dagger's out.
How come the supreme never told us that merging our Kwamis would grant us any wish we wanted?
For the same reason that he never told us that using our powers would slowly destroy us. No wish will save us.
?: Not with your miraculous no, but with Ladybug and Cat Noire’s most definitely.
- Cataclysm!
- Lucky Charm!
I am monarch, invulnerable to your powers thanks to the miraculous of the ox.
And I am also your best chance at having your wishes granted.
Are you willing to work with me, or would you rather keep on playing with your measly powers?
Delightful. It seems like we'll get along just fine. My plan is simple.
Tikki, spots on.
Plag, claws out!
We'll try to help you, betterfly.
- It’s Marinette, leave a message. Beep! Hehe.
- Ugh.
- They could be hiding anywhere.
- And they will do anything to get their hands on my miraculous.
Even in the darkest of nights, they won’t escape my sight.
CLAW NOIR: Betterfly!
- If you don't want us to destroy this world...
- Then come out, come out, wherever you are! You and your new buddies!
I guess they’re not hiding after all.
Monarch must have akumatized them.
What a holder of the butterfly miraculous has done, another can undo.
They're not akumatized villains.
You think Monarch could have lent them a miraculous?
- If that's true, we'll never defeat them.
- LADYBUG!
Wait for me here.
Alya, you can't stay here. It's dangerous. Is that my mom's phone?
It's a long story. Your mom is fine, but check this out.
My plan is simple.
Still nothing.
Are you sure your simple plan is going to work, Your Highness?
My plan is foolproof. They will show up.
Ladybug and Cat Noir always show up in the end.
PHONE: My plan is simple.
That's the room where I first arrived.
I was there for a sleepover at my friend Marinette's.
Your friend Marinette. Is she safe?
Yes i made sure of that.
And she's confirmed with me that she's okay.
- So the two giants out there are illusions?
- Created to trap you by forcing you two to split up.
- This is only the beginning of their trap.
And even though Alya recorded it all, no matter how much I think about it, play it back to myself.
I can't find any plan against a trap like this.
M’Lady, I know you're having a hard time right now.
You may not believe in yourself anymore, but I believe in you more than ever.
You're the best at finding the craziest ideas, even when everything seems lost.
It's like your lucky charms. They never make any sense, but they work every time.
He's right. Don't lose hope. I'm sure there's a solution.
I do have an idea, but I'm afraid it might be too convoluted.
We're all ears, Ladybug.
Okay. So first of all,
The miraculous of the butterfly has a limited range.
Past a certain distance, he can't keep in touch with the Akumas or the people he Akumatized.
We'll need to get far enough away from Paris to be out of Monarch's reach, so Betterfly can turn Alya into Ubiquity again.
- As long as we're far away, he won't be able to remove her power.
- That's right, Cat Noir.
Next, Betterfly will lend me the butterfly miraculous.
Light wings fall.
This way, I'll create a second superhero with a specially crafted superpower designed to protect Cat Noir and I.
Unify.
Next, we'll hide the object into which the kamiko will have landed into the parallel world.
Where it will be inaccessible to Monarch.
That way, Monarch won't be able to remove your powers during the battle.
And my power will protect you from the final treacherous blow Monarch plans to inflict upon you. Brilliant.
Now that's my lady.
The strength of teamwork.
See? They can't help themselves. They always have to save the world.
Maybe, but there are three of them, and Ladybug is wearing the miraculous of the butterfly.
Your supposedly simple two-person plan no longer works, Your Majesty.
On the contrary, now it will be even simpler to seize both their miraculous and the one of the butterfly.
As for the holder of the butterfly miraculous, whatever he has done regardless of his universe, I can undo it.
I'm sorry, Ladybug.
Thank you for your help, Alya.
It's you against me, giant Shadybug!
Ah!
Oh no! It was an illusion!
Mhm :)
It's your move. Voyage!
Surprise, Ladybug.
Ladyfly, actually. Nice to meet you. I love surprises.
Oh, could it be that it's just an illusion?
Voyage!
See you soon, my dear good king.
Nooroo, Kalki, Mullo, Pollen, Orikko, Unify.
Multiplication!
I hope you like a positively clawful cat fight!
Are you kidding me? The only thing worse than your fighting is your clawful puns.
- CLAW NOIR: With the right c’attitude, anything is possible!
- CAT NOIR: I literally can't believe we're the holders of the same miraculous!
- CLAW NOIR: You're a sly cat.
Ladybug!
Cat noir? Cat NOIR??
Are you lost without your little house pet?
Just because we're not together doesn't mean we're not working as a team!
CLAW NOIR: You're definitely not the cat in the out!
And you shouldn't count your cats before they scratch!
Fall in!
Where is this power coming from?
I can't feel any trace of akumitization.
Ah? It's a trap! Voyage!
Lucky charm!
I wouldn't break a mirror if I were you!
There's more seven years of bad luck, you know!
You think it'd be any different from how it is now?
Guess what? I don't have your nice little life!
In the world where I'm from, there are no awesome girlfriends to inspire me every day!
No amazing BFF, Let alone a mom!
A gentle mom or a boyfriend who doesn't think I'm a total loser!
Y-, You read my secret diary.
So you know we're the same, you and I.
UGH! Are you kidding? I'm the opposite of you!
All I've got in is pain and suffering from that horrible Chloe Bourgeois,
who made me suffer throughout my entire life until the Supreme entrusted me with the miraculous.
Now no one will hurt me anymore!
We have nothing in common!
You're wrong.
Reverse morphosis.
CAT NOIR: You know it's just a legend, right?
Yes I know! I know I am a legend!
CAT NOIR: I meant the one about cats not liking water.
Cats don't like water!
Well that's not true.
Some cats like myself are excellent swimmers.
I even have an aquatic version of my suit, don't you?
I hate water and swimming pools!
And conceited cats!
Conceited cats, conceited cats…
Hey now, I don't hear a pun there.
That's pretty unusual coming from you.
Huh?
You want a pun? Then brace yourself because until I get your miraculous,
I promise to dog your footsteps relentlessly!
Why do you have to have a miraculous that you already hold?
Don't you know?
We can make a wish by merging it with the cockroaches.
So you need ladybugs' miraculous, not mine!
- It doesn't work with our own, but with yours.
- You have no idea!
Merging these two miraculouses is too powerful! There would be a great price to pay!
- CLAW NOIR: Nothing is too powerful!
And there's no price too high to pay if it would bring my mother back!
- Your mother?
- She's gone!
And my father doesn't care! He's too crazy deciding dresses and costumes!
But is he creating things when he's already moved on?
But he has no idea how much I miss her!
I know.
If you read my diary then you know.
It's not all that easy.
Everything often hangs by a thread.
I too was very angry. I too was hurt. I too was scared.
And I still struggle with all of this every day.
You don't need any magic jewel. Powers didn't change my life.
I changed the way I saw myself.
I decided to love myself, to love the world around me.
And I decided that I could fix what was wrong in it.
I'm sure that if you change the way you see yourself and your world,
you'll be able to fix what's wrong with it too.
Just like I do here, every time.
You can fix it all.
I don't want to do that corny stuff.
By doing it in a way, you'll also fix yourself.
If I make a wish, I'll have a chance to get the only thing I want.
I'll bring her back to life. I'll see my mother again.
I know. I know you, you know.
No, you don't. Don't pretend to be me, or else you wouldn't be friends with a cockroach.
- If you were me, your mother would also be...
- She is.
But… if you knew about the wish, why haven't you tried it?
I won't tell you that I never thought about it.
Of course I thought about it. But…
Everything comes at a price if my mother came back.
Our mother!
In order to bring our mother back, someone else would have to lose theirs.
And that I can't wish on anyone.
Me? I managed to go on living, trying to be happy, as she wanted me to.
I have my friends to comfort me.
I'm okay now. I'm as well as I can be anyway.
It must be painful for someone who doesn't have any close friends, or anyone to comfort them.
Someone… like me?
Only you can decide not to be alone.
I can tell you about my friends from this world. You should meet them in yours.
You'd probably get along. Take Nino, for example.
Nino? I don't think he'd want to be buddies with me, considering how I treated him.
He's the most understanding person I know. Just apologize and invite him to the movies.
His favorite film, here anyway, is called Space Mutants vs. Ghost Shark.
It sounds terrible.
Let's say it's the film with the most improbable storyline I've ever seen.
And yet, you're really making me want to watch it.
Miraculous Shadybug!
Thank you.
Hey, I like your new look, Fancy Bug.
It wouldn't hurt you to do the same.
- Can I?
- You're the one who chooses your costume.
What do you want the new Claw noir to look like?
Meow! And now I'll be called Furrypaw, or the Wonder Whiskers, or Maid of Justice, or...
Ah, I just can't pick one.
What'll be yours?
Hmm. I'll call myself...
Ladybug.
*Cough*, Awful!
Hey! The best there is.
It's time. Alya Cesaire, if you'll allow me.
It's far from over, Ladybug. You may have escaped me once again in this universe, but it's only one among an infinity of others.
Nooroo, Orriko, Unify!
Sublimation.
The power of pretension allows me to choose a super ability. I choose access to any other existing universe.
I'm feeling a disruption, like another connection between universes is opening up at the same time as mine!
Monarch.
But how?
He has the Miraculous or the Rooster now, and can use it to create whichever superpower he wants.
Will he be able to travel across universes?
And attack every Ladybug in Cat Noir in existence?
I'll handle it.
Miraculous Scarabella.
Pound it!
Your earrings are mine!
It's not gonna happen in this world, Monarch.
Not here either!
No matter how far you get, you'll never, ever win!
Reverse Morphosis.
Ladybug, I will destroy you. You and every other Ladybug in all the parallel universes!
Monarch won't be going to any other world other than this one anytime soon, and here, Cat Noir, me and our friends, we'll make sure to put an end to his reign.
Even though we haven't figured out how to yet.
I am certain you will succeed. I thank you again for your help.
Thank you, Betterfly. You helped us get back something precious that we had lost.
Hope.
And you too have gained new teammates.
Yeah, by the way, we're gonna need a teammate, like the Supreme Movers. You know, a blend of Supreme and Removers. Get it. Get the joke.
Don't get smart, Fleabag. When the Supreme figures out that we're no longer on his side, we won't be laughing.
He won't be laughing either, believe me, because we'll be stronger now that we're together.
Remember that you have friends here.
And there are more friends are waiting for you on the other side.
Wait! In our world, we always do a little something when things end well.
Pound it!
huh? You okay girl?
Yeah, I was just thinking, life can really go in which way.
If we hadn't found ourselves sitting next to each other at the start of the school year,
I don't know if I would have become confident enough to become Ladybug. And who knows what would have happened today.
You made all the right choices, Marinette.
Do you remember what you told me on the first day of school?
All that is necessary for the triumph of evil is that good people do nothing.
I only made the right choice because you're a good person, Alya.
Oh, Marinette.
What if we made the right choice now and got some delicious breakfast?
Excellent choice. And then we're gonna take a little nap.
Hello, girls. How'd you sleep?
Very well, Mom.
Hey, Mrs. Dupain Cheng. Isn't that your phone over there?
Thanks, Alya. I couldn't find it anywhere.